beyblade.com 2006-06-16

# Privacy

**KIDS:**

Here's how Nelvana lets you have fun while protecting your privacy: 

* Our Privacy Policy recognizes and protects your right to privacy.
* We will not give, trade, sell or otherwise distribute any information you provide us.
* We will abide by all new laws that take effect in the future.
* We will collect some non-personal information, like the kind of browser and computer you use, so you can have the most fun possible whether you're at home or at school.
You also need to know how to protect yourself. For more tips on how to surf safely, visit our Web Safety page. 

**PARENTS:**

Our Principles

* We value your child's privacy - Nelvana Limited ("Nelvana") is committed to following all rules, policies and laws related to the collection of data and protecting the privacy of children and adults, and adhering strictly to our policy on information collection.
* We value your trust - Nelvana will not give, trade, sell or otherwise distribute the personal information you provide us.
* We value your online experience - To make your experience with us better and better, Nelvana reserves the right to analyze and summarize data that we collect. At times, we will share summaries of NON-PERSONAL data (e.g. percentage of girls vs. percentage of boys registered on our site) with sponsors or other business partners. We will never provide any specific or personally identifying information about an individual in any of these reports.
* We value your time - Registration should be easy and painless and access to, and the enjoyment of, any Nelvana web site, we feel is valuable in return.

Nelvana is committed to protecting your privacy and safety online. Nelvana encourages you, the adult, to check and monitor your child's online activities. Make sure your child knows to ask you before giving any personal information to any web site.

We have created this policy to explain why we ask for certain information when your child becomes a member, the types of information we gather, how it is used and how you or your child can change or delete the information.

Nelvana limits the collection of personal information from kids. For example, Nelvana does NOT ask for your child's full name or phone number. Nelvana will not intentionally post, sell, rent or disclose any personal information to any third parties.

**Why Do We Collect Information?**

At Nelvana we have created lots of fun activities that do not require you to provide any personal information at all. But by becoming a member of Beyblade.com and providing basic information to us, your child can receive email notifications of future site updates and promotions; and, he or she can enter our online contests as well as be notified if they are a contest winner (note: declarations and releases must be signed by a parent or guardian of the winner prior to Nelvana awarding or releasing the prize). Nelvana will never require kids to provide any more information than is reasonably necessary to participate in these activities. 

**How We Collect and Use Information**

**1\. Kids Registration Information** \- We ask for the following information when your child registers at www.beyblade.com: 

These things are required:   
a) Screen name and password   
b) Your child's birth date and gender   
c) The country (state/province) where you live   
d) A parent's email address (if the child is under 13 years of age)   
e) Your child's email address 

If your child submits his/her information to our site for membership and contest entry purposes, and is under the age of 13, an email permission form is sent to the parent's email address. Through this email, parents can review the information being collected from the child, and approve of our collection of the information for membership or have this information removed from our database.

Your child's email address is not required, but if you or your child requests our customized email news - that includes updates about activities and features, and your child's email address is provided, we can send it directly to your child. Otherwise, if you request our customized email news, without providing your child's email address we'll send it directly to your email address. If you (or your child) no longer wish to receive these messages, you can easily unsubscribe. Also, in keeping with Nelvana's belief in fostering family decisions about Internet use, members and parents may modify, review or delete information at anytime. 

Nelvana won't ask for more personal info that what we deem necessary and any information we collect will be stored in a secure database only accessible by Nelvana staff. 

Any personal identifiable info collected from our members is for Beyblade.com purposes only (e.g. membership verification, contest fulfillment, etc.) We will never sell or give any of this information to third parties. 

We use non-personal information - like gender, birth date, and country - to customize our site for our users. Sometimes we may share aggregate, non-personal information with our partners or advertisers (i.e. 20% of our members are boys from Ohio), however specific members are never identified.

**How to Modify or Cancel Your Account**

You can unsubscribe or modify/delete your child's subscriber information in one of two ways: 

* By email - You can unsubscribe using the instructions provided at the end of the email messages; or,
* By telephone - You can unsubscribe by leaving a message with Nelvana's Internet Membership Services at (416) 530-2825 extension 325. You will need all the information provided in our original confirmation message to you (your child's screen name, password, your email address, your child's date of birth and which features you would like us to have deleted. This will be implemented within 2 - 3 business days.

If you have any questions about our information practices and privacy policy, you may contact us at [webmaster@nelvana.com](mailto:webmaster@nelvana.com?Subject=Beyblade.com) (or send a letter to us at Internet Membership Services c/o Nelvana Limited, 32 Atlantic Ave., Toronto, Ontario, CANADA, M6K 1X8).

**2\. Passive Data Collection**

Cookies are small data files that your browser may place on your computer when you visit different Web sites to mark that you have been there. Nelvana only views the cookies that are set by our site and they do not provide us with any personal identifying information. These cookies help us collect aggregate data about the number of visitors to our site, how long they stay, what features and Web site activities are most often used. Cookies also help us determine general information about the types of computers, browsers and operating systems that are used to view our site - so that we can make sure that the technology we use to create our features can be viewed by our users. You may choose to set up your browser to refuse cookies or alert you when cookies are sent - but if you don't have a Nelvana cookie, it may limit our ability to customize and improve our features. 

**Links to Other Sites**

It is important to note that Beyblade.com contains links to sites or advertisements for sites outside Nelvana and beyond the control of Nelvana. These third party sites may not follow the same privacy policies as we do. They may also send their own cookies to your computer and collect data and make use of it in ways that Nelvana would not. Our site features a "bumper page" when linking to an advertisers' site to remind your child not to give out any personal information without checking first with a parent or guardian. Nelvana cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online and we must therefore advise that you do so at your own risk.

**How We Protect Personal Information**

Nelvana has established appropriate electronic, physical, contractual and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online to prevent unauthorized access, to maintain data accuracy, and to ensure the correct use of information. 

Any personal identifiable info collected from our members is for Beyblade.com purposes only (e.g. membership verification, contest fulfillment, etc.) We will never sell or give any of this information to third parties. We use non-personal information - like gender, birth date, and country - to customize our site for our users. Sometimes we may share aggregate, non-personal information with our partners or advertisers (i.e. 20% of our members are boys from Ohio), however specific members are never identified. 

**Learn More About Nelvana**

For more information about Nelvana - our vision and products - visit Nelvana's home page at www.nelvana.com or our each site's FAQ section. Email any questions to [webmaster@nelvana.com](mailto:webmaster@nelvana.com).

Please also make sure to read the Nelvana Terms and Conditions: They set out the rules for using all Nelvana sites. By using Beyblade.com you are agreeing to our Terms of Use.

Nelvana Limited  
Making Great Friends

TM and © 2004 Nelvana Limited
